so let's see if we understood how test
an atomic op locks work remember our
original code for load link store
conditional locks which loads the
previous state of the lock tries to put
one into the lock and then checks
whether we observed the unlock state of
the lock and whether we successfully
grab the lock so if we apply the test
and atomic up approach to this amazingly
we do that by just rearranging these
instructions the first two instructions
are exactly the same and then in what
order do we use the remaining three
instructions instead of writing out the
instruction just say which of these is
the instruction a B and C